go ahead Demetri please keep your
继续Demetri请保持您的
microphones metered if you're not
如果您不对麦克风进行测光
speaking there will be a lot of people
说话会有很多人
on the call okay so let's get started so
在通话中好吧，让我们开始吧，
this is basically a webinar about
这基本上是一个网络研讨会
creating cxd pipelines for a clicking
单击创建cxd管道
projector objects my name is Mitra
投影仪对象我的名字叫米特拉
kornilov I'm from Oracle and I'm also a
kornilov我来自甲骨文，我也​​是
forge a PMC member very gender for
为性别打造一个PMC成员
today's meeting is I will talk about the
今天的会议是我要谈的
minutes and it's mainly general
分钟，主要是一般的
information process overview progress
信息流程概述进度
straight in how to get help and this
直接获得帮助，这
kind of stuff
一种东西
after that we actually have to work 12
之后，我们实际上必须工作12
SGI CD pipelines and one is created by
SGI CD管道，其中一个由
Thomas Krause Jason he brought it he's
Thomas Krause Jason他带来了他的
going to talk about that for 20 minutes
谈论20分钟
after my presentation and the next one
在我的演讲和下一个演讲之后
is Marcus Clark
是马库斯·克拉克（Marcus Clark）
he is an author of workable jax-rs
他是《 jax-rs》的作者
Jackson even his pipeline he is going to
杰克逊甚至他要去的管道
explain in details after Thomas and in
在托马斯及其后详细解释
the last 10 minutes we are going to have
最后十分钟，我们将要
a Q&amp;A session if we finish early a Q&amp;A
如果我们提早完成问答，则会进行问答环节
session will be longer right so let me
会议时间会更长，所以让我
start sorry so general workflow which is
开始抱歉，所以一般的工作流程是
mainly for your understanding how their
主要是为了您了解他们如何
process works our goal is to I can hear
过程的工作目标是让我听到
someone is talking thank you so our goal
有人在说谢谢，所以我们的目标
is to release projects to OSS our H
是向OSS发布项目
stake in repository or assess our H is
入库或评估我们的H是
open source so no type repository
开源，所以没有类型库
hosting so nothing related to Red Hat
托管，所以与Red Hat无关
here so and after that we are planning
在这里和之后，我们正在计划
to release all artifacts to Maidan
将所有文物释放给Maidan
central but we can do it only after all
中央，但毕竟我们只能做到
integrations are done and all CGS dc-8s
集成完成，所有CGS dc-8
the past so release must be done from
过去的发布必须从
efore j 8 bridge we have all our
在8号桥之前，我们拥有了所有
repositories on
资料库
and there was a PMC request sometimes at
有时在PMC请求
the beginning of the year to create the
在今年年初创建
infiltrate branch I have a link to that
渗透分支我有一个链接
document in the slides I will show it to
幻灯片中的文档，我将显示给
you later
你以后
important thing is that if a j8 branch
重要的是，如果j8分支
must have a Georgian number which is a
必须具有格鲁吉亚数字，即
minor increase from the latest Oracle
与最新的Oracle相比略有增加
release so example is if the latest
发布，例如，如果最新
Oracle releases let's say to 100 j8
甲骨文发布100 J8
branch must contain 2 1 1 that rule and
分支必须包含2 1 1该规则和
just remind you that no API changes are
只是提醒您，没有API更改
allowed for now release must be done
现在允许释放必须完成
from eclipse Jenkins infrastructure and
来自Eclipse Jenkins基础架构和
it's done for security reason each foj
出于安全原因，每个foj
project has its own account in OSS RH
项目在OSS RH中有自己的帐户
and account details are hidden and
和帐户详细信息被隐藏，
available only to Jenkins jobs so
仅适用于詹金斯的工作，因此
Jenkins jobs must use maven Nexus
詹金斯的工作必须使用Maven Nexus
plug-in to make releases and the
插件发布和
credentials to OSS RH will be provided
将提供OSS RH的凭据
after magically by keeps infrastructure
经过神奇的维护基础设施
folks will explain how it works in a the
人们将解释它如何在
following presentation snowmachine
以下演示雪花机
Marcus and if it's not clear I clips via
马库斯，如果不清楚，我会通过
masters on the call so I can even
掌握电话，我什至可以
explain it better so in order to achieve
更好地解释它以便实现
that projects must request Jenkins
项目必须要求詹金斯
instance to be created first and after
实例先创建后
that project must provide a list of
该项目必须提供一个清单
released artifacts and request grant in
发布工件并请求授予
write access to their corresponding
对其对应的写权限
groups in or SSH to the project count
组或SSH到项目计数
and with request is done in eclipse
并在Eclipse中完成请求
Bugzilla again it's described in on the
Bugzilla再次在
wiki page so I created I will give links
Wiki页面，所以我创建了我将提供链接
to that later
到后来
and store motion Marcus will explain how
并存储动作Marcus将解释如何
jobs are leveraging made the Nexus
就业机会使Nexus
plug-in in their presentations progress
他们的演示进度插件
tracking
追踪
so how would throw track the progress
那么如何跟踪进度
basically it harp is our main source of
基本上，竖琴是我们的主要来源
truth and I personally created two tasks
真理，我个人创造了两个任务
in each he for a repository one task is
在每一个仓库中，一个任务是
Billy ICD pipeline so this is to create
比利ICD管道，所以这是要创建
a pipeline which builder projects and
建造者进行工程设计的管道，
another task is release a CD butterfly
另一个任务是释放CD蝴蝶
and this is a pipeline to release the
这是发布
project and this issue looks like that
项目，这个问题看起来像
so here is a sample of GPA project
这是GPA项目的示例
releases in the pipeline it has links to
它具有链接的管道中的发行版
the wiki document so you can click it
Wiki文档，因此您可以单击它
and get some instructions important is
得到一些重要的指示是
that project committers must self assign
项目提交者必须自行分配
to the tissue I see that this issue is
我看到这个问题是
not assigned yet issues must have a
尚未分配，问题必须有一个
build label so this is a label I created
构建标签，所以这是我创建的标签
for to sort of group up all these issues
为了将所有这些问题归类
together and it should be a part of IC
一起，它应该是集成电路的一部分
ICD pipelines project so I will touch a
ICD管道项目，所以我将涉及
little bit later actually now so it's
稍后实际上现在是
used for tracking the progress and it
用于跟踪进度及其
looks like this so you can access it if
看起来像这样，如果您可以访问它
you go to e for Jake organization and in
你去e为杰克组织和
projects there is a link to the ICD
项目中有指向ICD的链接
pipelines project it has three columns
管道项目有三列
to do in progress down and you see all
进行下去，您会看到所有
the issues here here is the nice
这里的问题很好
progress indicator it indicates that we
进度指示器，它表明我们
have five issues down 59 in progress and
有5个问题在进行中59个
twenty-three to do so that picture is
二十三张图片就是这样
much better than it was yesterday which
比昨天好多了
is very nice so when you self assign
非常好，所以当你自我分配时
yourself here to the issue your icon
自己在这里发布您的图标
will appear at the bottom right corner
将出现在右下角
and you also can move this card to do in
您也可以移动此卡在
progress right so then it's done you
进展顺利，然后就完成了
move to the down column
移至下栏
can do it yourself or I could do it for
可以自己做，也可以做
you I'm checking this page quite often
您我经常检查此页面
many times day so again github is the
一天很多次，所以github是
main source of truth
真理的主要来源
another tracking spreadsheet I have is
我拥有的另一个跟踪电子表格是
that I provided the link to that one and
我提供了到那个链接
which is mainly like for your
这主要是因为你
information I on the meetings to
有关会议的信息
demonstrate of all progress it has a
展示其所有进展
nice indication or in red there we have
很好的指示或那里有红色
on assigns tasks and live gray for
上分配任务，并为
repositories mission of interest short
知识库任务短
yet this kind of stuff
但是这种东西
again this is mainly for your
再次，这主要是为您
information you can comment here but
您可以在此处评论的信息，但
sorry of nothing else you can do here
对不起，您不能在这里做
please use it ha
请用它哈
next slide deadline so I will probably
下一个幻灯片的截止日期，所以我可能会
sell the completely shadow to the p.m.
把完全的影子卖给下午
cement is today or maybe tomorrow
水泥是今天还是明天
morning and because they are not quite
早上，因为他们不完全
sure lifter the plan yet but I think
肯定会取消计划，但我认为
what way I read on that deadline for CI
我在截止日期之前以什么样的方式阅读CI
CD tasks is first of October this year
CD任务是今年10月1日
so we still have two weeks to complete
所以我们还有两个星期要完成
all of these all of these right so it's
所有这些都对，所以它是
it's enough typed to it so hopefully we
它已经足够输入了，所以希望我们
will be able to achieve this data and
将能够获得这些数据，并且
possibly the main questions you have is
您可能遇到的主要问题是
how to get help so I created some Viki
如何获得帮助，所以我创建了一些Viki
pages so first of all here's a link to
页面，因此首先这里是一个链接
MC statement I mentioned on the first
我在第一个提到的MC陈述
slide this document looks like that you
滑动此文档看起来像您
have a legal of slides or semi slates
有合法的幻灯片或半单人
and slides and see the benefits after
和幻灯片，看看之后的好处
the meeting where is the wiki page about
Wiki页面所在的会议
how to release the first Eclipse version
如何发布第一个Eclipse版本
of projects on e4 JB key you have a link
e4 JB密钥上的项目集合，您有一个链接
and each release issue like that has a
每个这样的发行版都有一个
link to that as well
链接到那个
so general information release in maven
所以在Maven中发布一般信息
artifact links to some articles to how
工件链接到一些文章，以了解如何
to create the back information about
创建有关的背面信息
release review reviews on top of the
在顶部发布评论评论
based meeting but anyway you can check
会议，但无论如何您都可以查看
it and another link is
它和另一个链接是
this is what Thomas created he's going
这就是托马斯创造的他要去的
to present after me Jason PD nice job
向我介绍Jason PD表现不错
I'm not going to spend much time here
我不会在这里花很多时间
Thomas to explain it better right so you
托马斯更好地解释它，所以你
are welcome to create more pages if
欢迎创建更多页面，如果
something's not clear if you have a
不清楚是否有
better pipeline if you have any
有更好的管道
questions and you get answers you think
问题，您会得到答案，您认为
that others needs to know the answers
其他人需要知道答案
dat all wiki pages on our github in
将我们github上的所有wiki页面下载到
github repositories and advertise them
github仓库并做广告
in that mailing list right so these may
在该邮件列表中，这样
link miss D for Jade build many is this
链接D为Jade打造的小姐D是这个
last resort if you don't didn't find any
最后的手段，如果你没找到
information you need on the wiki pages
Wiki页面上所需的信息
just ask your question there we are all
只是问你一个问题，我们都
of these managers will be happy to help
这些经理将很乐意为您提供帮助
you so thank you very much thank you for
你，所以非常感谢你
joining this webinar thank you for
加入此网络研讨会，谢谢您
contributing to Jakarta EE I believe
我为Jakarta EE做贡献
that together we'll be able to to push
在一起，我们将能够推动
it forward that's it from my side and
从我这边向前就是
I'm passing presentation to Thomas
我正在向托马斯传递演讲
Krause who will explain his Jason
克劳斯（Krause）会解释他的杰森（Jason）
Pyrenees pipeline I'm stop sherry
比利牛斯管道我停止雪利酒
promise please yeah hello so and
答应，你好，所以，
mushrooms and I am also Oracle employee
蘑菇，我也是Oracle员工
and developer for many years I would
和开发人员多年，我会
like to tell you a couple words about
想跟您讲几句话
our builds and CI CD and release jobs
我们的版本和CI CD以及发布工作
for eg 4G projects
用于4G项目
Oh
哦
so mmm first of all I wanted to say a
首先，我想说一个
couple words about the article that
关于这篇文章的几句话
Mitra showed us before so this is the
Mitra之前向我们展示过，所以这是
big wiki page about real jobs and first
关于实际工作的Wiki大页面，第一个
thing that you have to do when you have
你必须要做的事情
a new project on Eclipse work is to get
Eclipse工作的一个新项目是
Jenkins environment for yourself so to
Jenkins的环境适合您自己
do so you cannot just set up all the
这样做，您不能只设置所有
things yourself but you have to open a
自己的东西，但你必须打开一个
back on Eclipse Bugzilla and ask for
回到Eclipse Bugzilla并询问
Jenkins instance to be created for you
为您创建的Jenkins实例
this Jenkins instance is created not
此Jenkins实例不是
fair github repository but per project
公平的github仓库，但每个项目
so usually one project has couple of
所以通常一个项目有几个
repositories and for all the group of
储存库以及所有
repositories you have just one Jenkins
你只有一个詹金斯仓库
instance to request the Jenkins instance
实例以请求Jenkins实例
you have to go through bugzilla here is
您必须通过bugzilla，这里是
the link and which goes here you have to
链接和去哪儿，你必须
open community park and just click on CI
打开社区公园，然后单击CI
Jenkins and put all the things that are
詹金斯，把所有的东西
required for your requests then you will
您的要求所必需的，那么您将
have to wait couple of days and then
必须等几天，然后
start implementing your build and
开始实施您的构建并
release jobs so now
现在发布工作
jobs itself I wanted to show things in
工作本身我想展示的东西
Jason B but as you can see I can't so I
杰森B，但如您所见，我做不到
have to do some work around let's go to
必须做一些工作让我们去
Jason B and here I have couple of jobs
杰森（Jason B）和我有几个工作
there so the most important at the
所以最重要的是
beginning is some continuous build job
开始是一些持续的工作
which is just about triggering the build
这只是触发构建
on github merges oh so this is the
在github上合并哦，所以这是
detail of the job there is nothing
工作细节没有
complicated just you have to configure
复杂，只需要配置
git repository policy I'm running let's
我正在运行的git仓库策略
say every hour or whatever you want and
说每小时或您想要的任何内容，
then just get some Java home
然后就把Java带回家
maven home and turn maven to do the
行家回家，转行去做
build for you and then you can display
为您建立，然后您可以显示
test results and other things this is
测试结果等
the easy one
简单的一个
if you want to do release job it's bit
如果你想做释放工作，那有点
more complicated so first problem is
比较复杂，所以第一个问题是
that in most cases we are trying to keep
在大多数情况下，我们试图保持
master branches in github read-only so
github中的master分支是只读的，所以
if you would like to release and dark
如果你想释放和黑暗
your revision then you should do things
你的修订，那么你应该做的事情
in separate branch which is then pushed
在单独的分支中，然后将其推送
back to the github and after then after
回到github，然后之后
that you can just create or request to
您可以创建或请求
merge it back to the master branch so to
合并回主分支，以便
do so I created bit more complicated job
这样做我创造了更复杂的工作
which starts with couple of parameters
从几个参数开始
maybe I can show show the interface
也许我可以显示界面
first so if we want to do the release we
首先，如果我们要发布，我们
have to provide some information so this
必须提供一些信息，所以这
is the release version then you need to
是发行版本，那么您需要
provide version of the next development
提供下一个开发的版本
cycle which is usually last version
周期，通常是最新版本
number plus one then which French to use
数字加一，然后使用哪种法语
for the release build and then I just
对于发布版本，然后我只是
added two check boxes one is that if you
添加了两个复选框，一个是，如果您
want to overwrite existing version with
想要覆盖现有版本
some fixes and if you want to do the dry
一些修复，如果你想干
run without pushing things into sumo
无需将任何东西推入相扑即可运行
type and github so now how this is
类型和github，所以现在这是怎么回事
implement it well first I need to define
首先要很好地实现它，我需要定义
the form with all the versions then
然后是带有所有版本的表格
gang get source code management I have
帮我获取源代码管理
to work with the branch that is coming
与即将到来的分支机构一起工作
from the forum and then another thing is
从论坛，然后另一件事是
SSH
SSH协议
so for accessing get help I need agent
因此要获得帮助，我需要代理
to be configured in the Jenkins CI this
在Jenkins CI中配置
is another thing you have to request in
是您必须要求的另一件事
your buck when you ask for creating to
当您要求创建
Jenkins instance and then the build
Jenkins实例，然后构建
script itself so at the beginning there
脚本本身，所以在开始时
are some environment there is some
有一些环境有一些
environment again maven Java one
环境再次Maven Java一
settings then I'm using some maven
设置，然后我正在使用一些行家
plugins to play this version now things
现在玩这个版本的插件
so first thing is to check that we are
所以第一件事就是检查我们
working with the snapshot and if not
使用快照，如果没有，
just serve an error and exit now the
只需提供一个错误并立即退出
thing is that in the forms you can just
事情是，在形式上你可以
fill a think and in that case it will
充满思想，在这种情况下，它将
try to compute all the versions itself
尝试自己计算所有版本
so there is some code this retrieving
所以有一些代码检索
current snapshot version then it's
当前快照版本，则为
trying to count release version and the
试图计算发行版本和
next development cycle versions and you
下一个开发周期版本，您
can see all of them and then there is
可以看到所有人，然后有
some code that is playing with the
一些正在使用的代码
branches and tags so if you check in
分支和标签，因此如果您签入
overwrite it will try to delete existing
覆盖它会尝试删除现有的
branch and talk in the github and
分支并在github中讨论
recreate them again then there is just
再次重新创建它们，然后
typical well in this case I'm not using
在这种情况下，我通常不会使用
my veneris plugin I am doing things
我的veneris插件我正在做事
manually so I have two versions plug-in
手动，所以我有两个版本的插件
to set the version then put things into
设置版本然后放进去
the hip-hop gate manually do the maven
街舞门手动做行家
[Music]
[音乐]
bail
保释
sign and deploy and at the end push push
签名并部署，最后推送
all the things into the github
所有的东西都放进github
unfortunately I cannot show you second
不幸的是我不能告诉你第二
where second script which contains
其中第二个脚本包含
release plug-in but I think it's
发布插件，但我认为是
available here on the wiki page so the
可以在Wiki页面上找到，因此
bigger page in the JSONP project
JSONP项目中更大的页面
contains all those things what are the
包含所有这些东西是什么
input parameters what they do how to
输入参数他们做什么
process our I'm processing them then how
处理我们我正在处理它们，然后如何
to take care of all the branches and
照顾所有分支机构
darks and here is the sample this maven
黑暗，这是这位行家的样本
release plug-in so question sorry yeah
发布插件，所以问题对不起
Thomas the comma and I don't know if
托马斯逗号，我不知道
this is for Dimitri or yourself this is
这是给迪米特里还是你自己的
Kevin Sutter I'm just kind of wondering
凯文·萨特我只是想知道
all of the scripting code that you're
您所拥有的所有脚本代码
showing us is this something that like
显示给我们的是这样的东西
is there a template that gets
有没有可以获取的模板
automatically populated for us or should
自动为我们或应该填充
we be cutting and pasting from your
我们正在剪切和粘贴您的
example or from Marcus's example I'm
或从马库斯的例子中我
just kind of wondering how do we get
只是想知道我们如何获得
started with the actual script yeah so
是从实际的脚本开始的，所以
the best thing is that at this moment
最好的是，此刻
you will probably have to copy paste
您可能需要复制粘贴
everything okay basically I duplicate it
一切都好，基本上我复制了它
I copy it all these streets to the VP
我将所有这些街道复制到副总裁
page which I sent link which were in my
我发送链接的页面
slides right Jason pitiless job so it's
滑动正确的Jason无情工作，所以
easy you just go to that page and you
容易，您只需转到该页面即可
will see all this code there and you can
将在那里看到所有这些代码，您可以
copy/paste to your job from there also
也可以从那里复制/粘贴到您的工作
on that wiki page there is a screenshot
在该Wiki页面上有一个屏幕截图
in PDF format of the whole of the
整个PDF格式
Jenkins job so you can see what other
詹金斯的工作，所以你可以看到其他
plugins are there and Thomas explained
插件在那里，Thomas解释了
what kind of Punkins are a little bit at
什么样的朋克有点
the beginner is
初学者是
yeah yeah it looks like that yeah it's
是的，看起来像那样，是的
here's the link so so sorry I'm using
这是链接，所以很抱歉我正在使用
Roberto from Tammy tribe so to clarify
塔米部落的罗伯托（Roberto）
so all the jobs from me for J should
所以我为J做的所有工作
follow this exact set up with all the
遵循所有的确切设置
same plugins all the same scripts
相同的插件，相同的脚本
everything like that is set up over here
像这样的一切都在这里设置
we are not forcing you to use our
我们不强迫您使用我们的
samples so you can use two jobs Thomas
样本，因此您可以使用两个作业Thomas
and Marcus's as a reference right so
和马库斯（Marcus）作为参考权利，所以
it's totally up to you you can copy it
这完全取决于您，您可以复制它
or you can come out with something else
或者你可以拿出别的东西
which achieves the same goal and if you
达到相同的目标，如果
do you're welcome maybe your solution
欢迎您，也许您的解决方案
will be better just if you do it better
只要做得更好就会更好
create a wiki page explain to us maybe a
创建一个Wiki页面，向我们解释一下
little copy okay I just clarify this I
小副本好吧，我只想澄清一下
don't want to make it better or or
不想做得更好或
actually have more work as that that you
其实还有更多的工作
don't want to make it better you
不想让它变得更好
shouldn't want well I'm pretty sure that
不应该很好，我很确定
you guys are fans all over there just
你们都是那里的粉丝
kidding okay yeah yeah but just take it
开玩笑吧，是的，但是就接受
easy all we wanted to do is just to
我们想要做的就是轻松
simplify it for everyone but if you
为所有人简化它，但如果您
wanted to do it your way
想按照自己的方式做
well it's up to so maybe I can I can
好吧，所以也许我可以
is gone so there are couple of more
不见了，所以还有更多
things to do so if you if the religion
如果你有宗教信仰的话
finishes it just pushes all the things
完成它只会推动所有事情
into github so there is new branch new
到github中，所以有一个新的分支
tag and all the artifacts are uploaded
标签，所有工件都已上传
into Sona type staging repository so you
到Sona类型登台存储库中，以便您
still have to do a couple of manual
仍然需要做一些手动操作
steps first one is you know to do
步骤第一步是你知道要做吗
additional distinct and close and do the
额外的不同和关闭，并做
release and law think is to take care of
释放和法律认为是要照顾
the branch so create or request for from
分支，因此创建或请求
it push it into the master and then if
它把它推入主人，然后如果
it's more project and just delete the
这是更多项目，只需删除
branch and for the big big project you
分支机构和大型项目
can keep it for sustaining and for minor
可以保留它来维持和维持轻微
releases oh there are still a couple of
发布哦，还有几个
things that are in my to-do list first
首先在我的待办事项清单中的事情
one is to automate those things so if
一种是使这些事情自动化，所以如果
it's possible to create a request for
可以创建一个请求
the branch from Jenkins and then play
詹金斯的分支，然后玩
with maven access plug-in to automate at
使用Maven Access插件自动执行
least closing things in staging Creepo
暂不准备Creepo的最后一件事情
but well unfortunately I don't I didn't
但不幸的是我没有
have enough time to do that so I think
有足够的时间来做，所以我认为
all from my side okay thank you very
都在我身边，很好，非常感谢
much
许多
are there any questions to trauma
对创伤有什么问题吗
no good so Thomas we stop sharing and we
不好，所以托马斯我们停止分享，我们
will pass presentation to Marcus
将演示文稿传递给马库斯
okay I hope you can see my scream I did
好吧，我希望你能看到我的尖叫
my best to check it before this mitri I
我最好在这个mitri之前检查一下
have a slightly different setup actually
实际设置略有不同
we also have three pipelines just saw in
我们还看到了三个管道
Tamil solution but we use different ways
泰米尔语解决方案，但我们使用不同的方式
to perform the same tasks I will start
执行相同的任务，我将开始
with the last one
与最后一个
Thomas ended with we have a file inside
托马斯结束了我们里面有一个文件
of our repository which is named Travis
名为Travis的存储库中
yml which triggers external pin service
触发外部引脚服务的yml
so this is not from the Eclipse
所以这不是来自Eclipse
Foundation this is some external company
基金会这是一些外部公司
and we use it because it's so deeply
我们使用它，因为它是如此深
integrated inch it up and it's really
整合起来，它真的
really easy you just provide a file like
真的很简单，您只需提供一个文件即可
this and it basically tells the service
这基本上告诉了服务
that we need several JVM and then it
我们需要几个JVM，然后
shows to the tool how to build our
向工具展示如何构建我们的
software so with normal maven call here
软件，因此通常的Maven可以在这里调用
so that's all there's nothing more to
因此，仅此而已
configure the only thing we asked
配置我们问的唯一一件事
Eclipse Foundation for is to allow that
Eclipse Foundation的目的是允许
external service to attach to our
外部服务附加到我们的狗屎
up repository so we opened a bug in the
资料库，所以我们在
Box Allah objectives foundation and
Box Allah的目标基础和
asked for doing this and that's all and
要求这样做，仅此而已
once you have this every commit you push
一旦有了这个每次提交，您就可以推送
ends up in an automated CI system which
最终出现在自动化的CI系统中
is already configured and build so we
已经配置并构建，所以我们
choose that way because it's just
选择这种方式，因为它只是
totally easy for external committers
外部提交者完全容易
or external contributors to have a CI
或外部贡献者拥有CI
system for every single branch and every
每个分支机构的系统
single fork without a need to configure
单叉，无需配置
anything the trick is that if we fork
任何诀窍是，如果我们分叉
the source code
源代码
oh we did it can use mine
哦，我们做到了，可以使用我的
always walking now it needs a while it
总是走现在需要一段时间
will copy that the Travis file so now we
将复制Travis文件，所以现在我们
have a fork and in there focus that
有叉子，在那里集中精力
Travis file and as I
Travis文件和我一样
of my own repository or my own account
我自己的存储库或我自己的帐户
for that trap is to to access
因为那个陷阱是要进入
I already have fully working so I can't
我已经完全工作了，所以我不能
click at that position I have an scooty
点击那个位置我有一个傻瓜
I have a completely running CI system so
我有一个完全运行的CI系统，所以
this is what Thomas said what is not
这就是托马斯所说的，不是
working and in solution right now
现在工作并处于解决方案中
because he had no time we didn't meet
因为他没有时间我们没见面
that time because it's really nothing
那个时候因为真的没什么
else than simply dropping in that single
除了简单地放下那个单曲之外
file and asking once the Eclipse
文件并询问一次Eclipse
Foundation to allow Travis echo so this
基金会允许特拉维斯回声，所以这
is how we work together with external
是我们与外部合作的方式
contributors so they can see if their
贡献者，以便他们可以查看他们的
code would do correctly the second thing
代码将正确地做第二件事
we get from them is this little icon we
我们从他们那里得到的是这个小图标
see here that says still passing we see
看到这里说仍然经过我们看到
this in the original one
这个在原来的
here we we have a URL given in that
在这里，我们有一个URL
readme file so we see if the master
自述文件，所以我们看看是否掌握
branch builds correctly that's a small
分支构建正确，这很小
gimmick but it's pretty cool okay now
头，但是现在挺酷的
getting back to the original question of
回到原来的问题
releasing we also asked the Eclipse
发布我们还问了Eclipse
Foundation with the popular tools that
用流行的工具打基础
we want to have our own instance of
我们想要拥有我们自己的实例
Jenkins and that we need access for OS s
Jenkins，我们需要访问OS
rh it's exactly the same way to set it
rh设置方法完全相同
up that Thomas already explained so idle
托马斯已经解释得很闲
repeaters inside of our champions we
冠军内部的中继器
have two tasks one simply does nightly
有两个任务，一个只是每晚做
builds I come back to this one later and
建立我稍后再回到这个
one is for the official release and this
一个是用于正式发布的
is pretty simple I'm going into
我要讲的很简单
configuration and what it basically does
配置及其基本功能
is that it pulls the source code from
是它从中提取源代码
github and it only selects the EE for j8
github，它仅选择j8的EE
branch so we are sure that you're really
分支，因此我们确定您确实
releasing what Mitra wants us to release
释放Mitra希望我们释放的东西
and nothing else so the last step is
没有别的，所以最后一步是
that it triggers maven and in May 1 we
它触发了行家，在5月1日，我们
have a special configuration this is
有一个特殊的配置，这是
what if mine is P does it ours in this
如果我是P怎么办呢？
string named release to enable a special
名为release的字符串以启用特殊功能
mode they call it profile my colleague
他们称之为个人资料我的同事的模式
mode and I will show what it up
模式，我将展示它
so inside of our API project we have the
因此，在我们的API项目中，
PLM I hope you can really like try to
PLM希望您真的可以喜欢尝试
enlarge it a bit and inside of this we
扩大一点，在这个里面
have this
有这个
really somewhere I'll help where is his
我真的会在某个地方帮助他
profile okay
个人资料还可以
let's search for the profile no let's
让我们搜索个人资料不让我们
let it
让它
no no one
不，没人
oh I'm I'm in the wrong I'm in the wrong
哦，我错了我错了
branch that's the proper line to go to
分支是要转到的正确行
be 48
是48
okay what
好吧什么
okay there is okay now
好吧，现在好了
profile they're just so we have to
简介他们只是，所以我们必须
profile named really so this must be the
个人资料的名称确实如此，因此必须是
same string it it does not need to be
相同的字符串，它不必是
released exactly you can name it X or Y
完全发布即可命名为X或Y
so it's just for readability and by this
所以这只是为了提高可读性
string we see what we will ask maven to
字符串，我们将看到我们将要求Maven执行的操作
do actually and what it does is let in
实际去做，然后去做
some plugins in particular Nexus station
一些Nexus Station专用的插件
plug-in which is simply there for asking
插件只是在那里问
on OSS our age to open a staging every
在我们这个时代开放的OSS
where we can put in files that we want
我们可以在其中放入所需的文件
to release without actually releasing
释放而不实际释放
them so they're in some kind of suspense
他们，所以他们处于某种悬念中
until we press the trigger
直到我们按下扳机
this is needed because in fact we don't
这是必需的，因为实际上我们不需要
want a single artifact to be released
希望发布单个工件
and we don't want to release right now
而且我们现在不想发布
so it simply collects the original trial
所以它只是收集原始审判
file the sauce draw the Javadoc char the
归档酱绘制Javadoc char
the numbers given by pizzas by cpg which
cpg给出的披萨数量
is the second plugin which runs here and
是第二个在这里运行的插件，
then it simply will stop it will not
那么它只会停止它不会
actually push to OS SRH at that moment
当时确实推送到OS SRH
we ask for a review with the PMT and CMO
我们要求与PMT和CMO进行审查
and when the review is done then we go
当审查完成后，我们开始
into the the nexus staging area we have
进入连结分期区
given from sona type access to that
从sona类型访问
prior to that browser interface so there
在该浏览器界面之前，因此
is more button called
被称为更多按钮
release and we just manually press
释放，我们只需手动按
release so actually our script is not
发布，所以实际上我们的脚本不是
able to release it just prepares to
能够释放它只是准备
release and the actual release is done
发布并完成实际发布
manually a real person clicking on that
手动点击一个真实的人
okay and what we have fear also is that
好吧，我们担心的是
we need to create javadocs between it we
我们需要在它们之间创建javadocs
actually don't need to release plug-in
实际上不需要释放插件
this this is from all the times I just
这是我一直以来的一切
forgot to remove it actually we create
忘记删除它实际上是我们创建的
the hash codes for your artifact and
您的工件的哈希码和
then we tell maven not to invoke the
然后我们告诉Maven不要调用
original deploy plugin because um this
原始的部署插件，因为这个
will do the wrong things that we say
会做我们说的错误的事情
skip instead of that we invoke that next
跳过而不是调用下一个
staging plug-in which
暂存插件
runs at the deploy task is a bit
在部署任务上运行有点
confusing because it's the same name and
令人困惑，因为它是同名的
and here's the configuration
他妈的，这是配置
where all this shall happen so this is
这一切都会发生的地方
the server from OSS our age where all
来自OSS时代的服务器
the stuff ends up and this one tells not
东西结束了，这个告诉不
to automatically release so it actually
自动释放，所以它实际上
shall stop when it's all uploaded so the
全部上传后应停止，因此
next part here and that's the end of the
下一部分，到此结束
profile is that we have a repository on
简介是我们有一个存储库
OSS our age which we need to give the
OSS我们的时代，我们需要给予
actual URL because the champion server
实际网址，因为冠军服务器
does not know well it's it's basically
不太清楚，基本上是
it is the same one for all projects in
对于所有项目来说都是一样的
checkers and ricotta but deserved chest
跳棋和意大利乳清干酪，但应得的胸部
does not know so every project has to
不知道，所以每个项目都必须
repeat this this one is not needed we
重复这个，这是不需要的，我们
actually don't do snapshots on ours at
实际上不对我们的快照
our age we have a different pipeline for
我们这个时代我们有不同的渠道
that one micro sorry I can interrupt you
那个微微抱歉，我可以打扰你
little bit I think that this repository
我认为这个仓库
information is actually in the parent
信息实际上在父项中
form right so you just repeat it here
表格正确，所以您只需在这里重复
because you are not using the e4j parent
因为您没有使用e4j父对象
form is it correct yes that's correct
形式是否正确是是正确的
because I'm just for those who want to
因为我只适合那些想要
use a parent on the parent form is fine
在父母表格上使用父母是可以的
actually but it is incompatible with
实际上，但是与
what we do here with our snapshot the
我们在这里用快照做什么
parent form actually would do normal
家长表格实际上会正常
nightly build also on OSS our age and we
每晚也基于我们这个时代的OSS
don't do that so we actually don't use
不要这样做，所以我们实际上不使用
this one
这个
we need our original servers here
我们需要这里的原始服务器
because we are using the Eclipse
因为我们正在使用Eclipse
organization nexus for our nightly build
我们每晚构建的组织关系
so this is cannot yeah
所以这是不可能的
certainly fine comment is that if
当然好的评论是，如果
project actually uses Evo Jake parent
项目实际上使用了Evo Jake父级
form then and would like to also deploy
表单，然后还希望部署
their nightly builds then these
他们的每晚建筑，然后这些
configuration you're demonstrating now
您正在演示的配置
is not needed correct
不需要正确
yeah that is absolutely correct this is
是的，这是绝对正确的，这是
what I wanted to say yeah great thanks
我想说的是，非常感谢
if you stick with the parent pom you
如果你坚持父母的pom
don't need to have to copy all this I
不需要复制所有这些我
just want to show because we do not use
只想显示，因为我们不使用
that term from then it's a bit shorter
从那时开始，这个词要短一些
here okay but I think you got the idea
好的，但是我想你知道了
so we are not using this one in release
所以我们不在发行版中使用这个
mode we use the other section in release
模式，我们使用发布中的另一部分
mode if we are not in release mode then
模式，如果我们不处于发布模式，则
we are using this repository and the
我们正在使用该存储库，
difference release mode or not is where
差异释放模式与否
is it
是吗
is here so we do this only if we really
在这里，所以只有在我们真的
want to do an official release if we
想要发布正式版本，如果我们
want to do an arc appeals we don't have
想做一个我们没有的弧线上诉
this one here
这一个
okay so back
好吧，回来
- the naughty girls might abuse are a
-顽皮的女孩可能会虐待
bit more complex because we wanted to
有点复杂，因为我们想
have nightly builds for several branches
每晚有几个分支的版本
so we use a special plug-in that is
所以我们使用一个特殊的插件
already installed on Eclipse Foundation
已经安装在Eclipse Foundation上
Jenkins we didn't know that plug-in
Jenkins我们不知道该插件
before we had a lot of great help from
之前我们有很多很大的帮助
the Eclipse Foundation administrators to
Eclipse Foundation管理员可以
get it running and what this does is
让它运行，这是什么
that it it actively checks for the
它会积极检查
existing branches so we need a
现有分支机构，所以我们需要一个
configuration for this to make it work
为此进行配置
and if you want to follow this it's best
如果你想遵循这个最好
to look what we have done in our
看看我们在我们所做的
repository this is another story there's
仓库，这是另一个故事
another configuration file called
另一个配置文件称为
Jenkins file this Jenkins file actually
詹金斯档案实际上是这个詹金斯档案
is a configuration for the multi branch
是多分支的配置
nightly builds us and what it does is it
每夜建立我们，它所做的是
basically says
基本上说
you shall regularly trigger build so we
您应定期触发构建，因此我们
wanted one tonight
今晚要一个
we need JDK and maven
我们需要JDK和Maven
Oh with shortcut for for calling maven
哦，有个调用maven的捷径
here and then it's setting up stages we
在这里，然后建立阶段，我们
have a single stage called Maggie build
有一个称为Maggie build的阶段
and this shall only run for select
这只能用于选择
branches
分行
actually it should not run for this one
实际上它不应该为此运行
is not good and then it does steps and
不好，然后执行步骤，
the step number one is we want to
第一步是我们要
compile our API draw file and step
编译我们的API绘图文件并执行步骤
number two is we want to compile our
第二是我们要编译我们的
examples for widow and this is
寡妇的例子，这是
automatically done for every branch so
每个分支自动完成，因此
if we go into this one so yeah right
如果我们进入这个，是的，对吧
pipeline we will see a graphic so we can
管道，我们将看到一个图形，所以我们可以
see the stages here and we can see the
在这里看到阶段，我们可以看到
bills automatically triggered every
账单自动触发
night here and this is quite neat
晚上在这里，这很整洁
actually it's not working perfectly yet
实际上它还不能很好地工作
we're working on this but this is this
我们正在为此工作，但这是这个
is a cool thing because we can have a
是一件很酷的事情，因为我们可以拥有
nightly build made up for feature
每晚构建以弥补功能
branches we want to work with future
我们希望与未来合作的分支机构
branches in future and so every feature
将来会分支，所以每个功能
branch would have its own my hypnose so
分支会有自己的催眠，所以
that's basic idea and we don't have to
这是基本的想法，我们不必
configure a lot we can exclude branches
配置很多我们可以排除分支
we don't need to have to I know that so
我们不需要一定要知道
it's still working progress but it's
它仍在工作中，但是
pretty cool yeah that's basically it if
是的，很酷，如果
you have any questions then start asking
您有任何问题，然后开始问
hi I have one question is there any main
嗨，我有一个问题，有没有主要的
reason why the nightly bills are based
每晚账单依据的原因
upon a Jenkins pipelines versus they did
在詹金斯管道上，他们做了
the other one that is made in the
另一个是在
Yankees UI um actually it's a bit of
Yankees UI嗯，实际上有点
historic reason we started with Travis
我们从特拉维斯开始的历史原因
which worked rather well the Travis
特拉维斯效果很好
known highly build it goes at once
众所周知的高度构建一次完成
though it's more often which is better
虽然更多更好
but we wanted to have the possibility to
但我们希望有可能
fill the binary artifacts into a Nexus
将二进制工件填充到Nexus中
server and Eclipse Foundation told us we
服务器和Eclipse Foundation告诉我们
cannot give the configuration for
无法提供配置
uploading into a nexus server in a
上传到一个
public system like Travis so we may not
像Travis这样的公共系统，所以我们可能不会
write it into the Travis file so they
将其写入Travis文件，以便他们
told us we may upload into their own
告诉我们我们可以上传到自己的
Nexus server but this is only possible
Nexus服务器，但这仅是可能的
from Jenkins this is not possible from
从詹金斯这是不可能的
Travis so we started with Jenkins for
特拉维斯（Travis），所以我们从詹金斯（Jenkins）开始
nightly build and then we learned that
每晚构建，然后我们了解到
anyway we have to use Jenkins for
无论如何，我们必须使用詹金斯
publishing the release so now the next
发布该版本，所以现在下一个
step would be to get rid of Travis and
步骤将是摆脱特拉维斯和
replace it by Jenkins but this would be
用詹金斯代替它，但这将是
a real lot of work but so as it is
大量的工作，但实际上
running anyway we just stopped work on
无论如何，我们只是停止工作
this transition and now we live with
这种过渡，现在我们与
both words in parallel because it's
两个字平行，因为
simply working at the moment maybe we
目前只是工作，也许我们
will get rid of Travis I don't know
会摆脱我不知道的特拉维斯
thank you
谢谢
yeah mine was something similar with
是的，我的与
that because of Jenkins and Travis if
因为詹金斯和特拉维斯
you were going to be posed or if you're
你将被摆姿势，或者如果你是
going to get rid of Travis
要摆脱特拉维斯
yeah as I said at the moment we stick
是的，正如我在此刻所说的，我们坚持
with both it's working great and maybe
两者都很好，也许
we will get rid of Travis when we learn
当我们学习时，我们将摆脱特拉维斯
to configure Jenkins to automatically do
将Jenkins配置为自动执行
the bills for anonymous people I don't
我没有的匿名人士的账单
know if that is any possible because
知道是否有可能，因为
this would need to have a better
这需要一个更好的
integration between Jenkins and cheetah
詹金斯与猎豹之间的融合
so it depends on the actual needs to go
所以要看实际需要去
away from Travis and it depends on a lot
远离特拉维斯，这取决于很多
of work to make it work in Jenkins I see
使它在詹金斯工作的方法
it a different way so so getting rid of
这是一种不同的方式，所以摆脱
Jenkins it's not possible we we must
詹金斯我们不可能
have Jenkins you cannot push to OSS RH
有詹金斯你不能推到OSS RH
or true the Eclipse Foundation's Nexus
或是Eclipse Foundation的Nexus
without Jenkins only champions can do
没有詹金斯，只有冠军才能做到
that is this is Jenkins are you able to
这就是詹金斯吗
see Jenkins builds and basically reports
查看Jenkins的构建并基本上报告
all that stuff it's never there
所有这些东西永远都没有
anonymously or do you need an account so
匿名还是您需要一个帐户，所以
you audio is a bit screwed I didn't
你的音频有点搞砸了，我没有
really understand let me try to speak a
真的很明白，让我试着说
little bit clearer I was asking if you
我问你是否清楚一点
required an account to check all the
需要一个帐户来检查所有
Jenkins stuff or if you were able to at
詹金斯的东西，或者如果您能够
least see the reports and the bill the
最少查看报告和账单
status with an anonymous account
匿名帐户的身份
actually no count at all actually the
实际上根本不算什么
Jenkins account here it's from the
詹金斯的帐户来自
Eclipse Foundation so I'm logging it
Eclipse Foundation，所以我正在记录它
does not work and at least I I think
不起作用，至少我认为
though that it does not work anonymously
虽然它不能匿名工作
I think it will only work with accounts
我认为这仅适用于帐户
so that's one problem where Travis is
这是特拉维斯所在的问题之一
great because Travis works with the
太好了，因为Travis与
cheetah account and everybody has a
猎豹帐户，每个人都有
cheetah account I believe that only
猎豹账号我相信只有
project commuters have access to the
项目通勤者可以使用
project
项目
Jenkins instance so this is why it's a
詹金斯实例，所以这就是为什么
problem for you
给你的问题
to see a JSONP release job or jax-rs
查看JSONP发布作业或jax-rs
release job because you simply not
释放工作，因为你根本不
committer in that project and you won't
该项目的提交者，您将不会
have access this is one of the reasons
有访问权限，这是原因之一
why I created the screenshot and the
为什么我创建了屏幕截图和
face of the source code to the wiki
Wiki的源代码外观
pages
页数
you
您
yeah I think if I if I log off I think
是的，我想如果我注销，我想
yeah it's gone I don't see anything
是的，它消失了，我什么也没看见
yeah but even even usually even if you
是的，但即使是平时，即使你
may set it up in a way that only
可能会以仅
commuters can change and edit jobs but
通勤者可以更改和编辑工作，但
people from website can still see the
网站上的人仍然可以看到
results I'm not sure if that's a
结果我不确定这是否是
possible policy or I think it's a
可能的政策，或者我认为这是一个
question to eclipse webmasters I'm sure
我敢肯定，这个问题会让网站管理员黯然失色
so apparently we had to limit the
所以显然我们不得不限制
permissions for anonymous users for
匿名用户的权限
legal reasons and as far as I understood
法律原因，据我了解
this might not this might change in the
这可能不会改变
future again but for now we are required
再次的未来，但现在我们需要
to not give access to the public to
不向公众开放
tribute builds and the artifacts cleared
致敬构建并清除工件
or not Fredrik thank you and if that's
还是Fredrik谢谢你，如果那是
it if this topic I wanted to mention one
如果这个话题我想提一个
thing Marko's you said that to actually
Marko是你说的
make it release you need to go to or SS
释放它，您需要进入或SS
RH react page and manually press the
RH反应页面，然后手动按
button this is actually what we would
按钮，这实际上是我们想要的
like to avoid right because you need to
喜欢避免权利，因为您需要
have your personal account which has
有您的个人帐户
rights to the Java X groups in OSS our
OSS中Java X组的权利
age right so for security reasons the
年龄正确，因此出于安全原因
idea was that only Eclipse project
想法是只有Eclipse项目
account has these rights right and to
帐户拥有这些权利，并有权
actually make it release we need to
实际发布它，我们需要
create possibly another Jenkins job
创造另一个詹金斯工作
which is trigger it manually which will
这是手动触发它会
actually simulate pressing the button
实际模拟按下按钮
and make the actual remains
并留下实际的遗骸
that's my goal yes in fact what you
那是我的目标，是的，事实上你
could do is use the plugin I showed
可以做的就是使用我显示的插件
before because the next staging plug-in
之前，因为下一个暂存插件
actually could release it could
实际上可以释放它可以
virtually press the button now so it's
实际上现在按下按钮，所以
the 100 on just a second they chained
他们连锁的那一秒钟的100
again the zero on this one there's it's
再次在这个零是
teaching display it's called next
教学展示，称为下一个
staging plugin with actually it's a
分期插件，实际上它是一个
complete remote control for OSS RH so
完整的OSS RH远程控制，因此
you could simply set up another profile
您可以简单地设置另一个配置文件
here which would virtually trigger the
这实际上会触发
button and you could offload the login
按钮，您可以卸载登录名
information inside of the configuration
配置内的信息
of the Jenkins so we have I don't know
詹金斯一家，所以我们不知道
if everybody's well what Jenkins can do
如果每个人都健康，詹金斯能做什么
that there is a secret store which would
那里有一个秘密商店
hold the login information so you can
保留登录信息，以便您可以
trigger the button without going on the
触发按钮而不继续
the browser page actually
实际的浏览器页面
yeah which is exactly the call and you
是的，这正是电话，而你
just explained that it's possible to do
只是解释说有可能做
and the original idea of originally was
最初的想法是
to do it exactly as you explain now
完全按照您现在的解释进行
you
您
okay are there any more questions
好，还有其他问题吗
otherwise I would say it's between time
否则我会说这是时间之间
again then I stopped sharing to meet you
再一次，我不再分享见到你
there's a couple of questions in the
有几个问题
chat can you shoot first of all I would
聊天你可以先拍摄吗
like to say thanks for Maricruz for
想对Maricruz表示感谢
perfect presentation and let me check
完美的演示文稿，让我检查一下
the patient's yeah from Jim our
病人是吉姆
automatic bills required to be set up or
需要设置的自动帐单或
should we work with the owners to
我们应该与业主合作
determine if they are required I think
确定是否需要它们，我认为
the answer is that automatic builds you
答案是自动建立您
mean a what you mean nightly or I
意思是你每晚或我的意思
supposed to nightly builds it's
应该每晚建造
completely up to you the project if you
如果您完全取决于您的项目
want to publish nightly builds free to
想要免费发布每晚版本
do that if you don't want to publish
如果您不想发布，请执行此操作
nightly builds it's okay for instance we
每晚构建都可以，例如我们
are not publishing nightly builds for
不发布有关
Jason P in Jason B because well it's not
Jason B中的Jason P，因为它不是
point right but after Matic build is
指向正确，但是在Matic建立之后
definitely needed there if you want to
如果你想肯定在那里
release the project right so before
立即发布项目
releasing something you need to build it
释放您需要构建的东西
right so this is why we have two jobs
对，所以这就是为什么我们有两个工作
two tasks created one is to build the
创建了两个任务，一个是构建
project and another one to release what
项目和另一个发布什么
you just build I hope you are a caballo
你刚刚建立，我希望你是一个caballo
answers yeah I was mostly thinking about
是的，我主要在想
whether or not Knightley's were needed
是否需要奈特利
or not and this is top-down right so
还是不，这是自上而下的，所以
release is hundred percent mean it right
释放百分百表示正确
but Knightley's now as I said we don't
但奈特利现在是我所说的
do it for Jason P and Jason B because we
为Jason P和Jason B做到这一点，因为我们
are not really contributing therefore
因此没有真正的贡献
every day right api's are not usually
每天正确的api通常不
changing their often so I don't see that
经常改变他们，所以我看不到
we need nightly builds okay okay so
我们需要每晚构建好吧好吧所以
other questions
其他问题
questions there
那里的问题
those hit things
那些撞东西
now uhyou here is a question ah bill
现在你这是一个问题啊法案
three soldiers need for all projects
所有项目都需要三名士兵
marked as to do on the spreadsheet
标记为在电子表格上执行
basically as I is from Scott as I said
就像我说的那样，我来自斯科特
the main source of through is it hub
贯通的主要来源是枢纽
right so all issues all unassigned
对，所以所有问题都未分配
issues on github we need someone to work
github上的问题，我们需要有人工作
on that so yes we need contributors we
在那上面，是的，我们需要贡献者，我们
have a slight problem the problem is to
有一个小问题，问题是
work with Jenkins go to request the job
与詹金斯（Jenkins）合作，要求这份工作
created to make diffic Asian's to
创建以使亚洲人难以接受
drinking jobs you must be a project
喝酒你必须是一个项目
committee so we found that you won't
委员会，所以我们发现您不会
have access to Jenkins there is a
有机会进入詹金斯
workaround and workaround is create a
解决方法和解决方法是创建一个
Jenkins file but Jenkins job well
詹金斯档案，但詹金斯表现不错
similar to but not see but like that
类似于但看不到但类似
what Mark was shot on his presentation
马克在演讲中被枪杀了什么
may committers review that publish sheet
可能使提交者审查该发布表
and some of the commuters will update
一些通勤者会更新
Jenkins instance this is a bit
詹金斯实例这有点
complicated so I I am suggesting that
很复杂，所以我建议
you self-assign only to see ICD tasks
您只进行自我分配即可查看ICD任务
only if you're committed of the project
仅在您致力于该项目时
to make it to make it faster to make
使它变得更快
less complicated for yourself
自己不那么复杂
other questions hi this is Scott again I
其他问题嗨，这又是斯科特我
just I had asked that question
只是我问过这个问题
I'm not a committer or on any of the
我不是提交者，也不是任何
projects willing to volunteer to help I
愿意自愿帮助我的项目
would think you becoming a committer on
会认为你成为一个提交者
some project might be the way a easier
一些项目可能更容易
path like like you just said does that
就像你刚才说的那样
make sense for those of us that aren't
对于那些不是我们的人有意义
committers to pick a project to help on
提交人选择一个项目来帮助
and then become a committer or is that
然后成为提交者，或者是
not reasonable in this timeframe I will
在这个时间范围内我不合理
forward these questions to eclipse false
转发这些问题以掩盖错误
because folks are online right now the
因为人们现在在线
right way to do it is to are
正确的方法是
contributing to the project if there's
为项目做贡献
some reason for some reason the project
由于某种原因该项目
team is unable to respond to your
团队无法回应您
contribution that we have some
我们有一些贡献
mechanisms to help there is this thing
帮助有东西的机制
on it is we lived
关于它我们住
okay Scott did you did--we in answer a
好吧，斯科特，你做了吗？
question
题
so I mean I've contributed to eclipse
所以我是说我为日食做出了贡献
link you know maybe at five or six years
链接，您可能知道大概五六年
ago but I'm not a committer I mean on
以前，但是我不是提交者
that so so the projects are operating on
这样项目就可以在
github and they will they accept pull
github，他们将接受拉
requests if you have other contributions
要求您是否还有其他贡献
to make then make that like the way to
使然后使像这样的方式
become a committer is you start by
成为提交者，是从头开始
making contributions to the project and
为该项目做出贡献
contributions can come in the form of
捐款的形式可以是
code they can come in the form of
代码可以以以下形式出现
contribution other other forms of energy
贡献其他其他形式的能量
you know again if the project team is
你再次知道项目团队是否
unable to respond for whatever reason
无论出于什么原因都无法回应
then I can figure I can figure out
那我就可以算出
places to deal with that problem with by
解决这个问题的地方
and large most of these projects should
这些项目大多数都应该
have committers that are active that
有活跃的提交者
should respond to your employ yeah note
应该回应您的雇用
mostly I want to help with some of the
我主要是想帮助一些
you know creating the release plugin I
你知道我创建发布插件
mean the release jobs the CI integration
意味着发布工作是CI集成
CI CD integration and I think we
CI CD集成，我认为我们
previously just said it's most effective
以前只是说这是最有效的
if you are a committer already to do
如果您已经是提交者了
that so I'm just trying to figure out if
所以我只是想弄清楚
there is a path for non committers to
非提交者有一条通往
effectively help out quickly enough and
有效地提供足够的帮助
I think what you're saying I understand
我想你在说什么我明白
what you're saying about becoming a
你在说要成为一个
committer and yeah I don't particularly
提交者，是的，我不是特别
care about becoming a committer for this
关心成为这个的提交者
timeframe but I I do want if I you know
时间表，但是我确实想知道
do a help on some of these to do tasks
帮助其中一些任务
I'd like it to be in an effective
我希望它能有效
experience not have it be long and you
经验不长，你
know slow and dry though I suppose you
虽然我想你知道我又慢又干
know to do each change through pull
知道通过拉来做每个改变
request I guess so I'm not maybe I
要求我猜所以我也许不是
missed something and I'm not clear about
错过了一些东西，我不清楚
how we help as non committers basically
我们基本上如何作为非提交者提供帮助
if your help if you would like to help
如果您有帮助，如果您想帮助
in CIC / its right then you said that
在中投公司/它的权利中，那么你说
you would like to configure nexts
您想配置下一个
plugins right so in order to do that you
正确的插件，以便您这样做
actually don't need to have access to
实际上不需要访问
the Jenkins repository the repository
Jenkins存储库存储库
instance right so I'm suggesting that
实例正确，所以我建议
you make your job after that you submit
你提交之后就做你的工作
a TR to the project which has your
有您的项目的TR
modified pom.xml right with edit profile
使用编辑配置文件修改了pom.xml
added Nexus plug-in right so committers
正确添加了Nexus插件，因此提交者
will give you that right and test it on
会给你正确的权利并对其进行测试
the real Jenkins the instance you won't
真正的詹金斯你不会的实例
have access to there because of Eclipse
由于Eclipse而可以访问那里
restrictions so this is the problem I
限制，所以这是我的问题
was talking about but the help is
在谈论，但帮助是
definitely appreciated so if you want to
绝对感激，所以如果你想
do it we are very very welcome select a
做到这一点，我们非常非常欢迎选择
project from the github page you can
您可以从github页面进行项目
port I demonstrated and start working on
我演示的端口并开始研究
this and thank you very much for your
这个，非常感谢你的
Wilander contribute is it okay it's
威兰德（Wilander）贡献是好的
called
叫
I can't hear you oh so sorry
我听不到你的声音，对不起
yeah I mean I I think we should try and
是的，我是说我认为我们应该尝试
move forward I just wanted to make sure
前进，我只是想确保
I understood exactly how we thought this
我完全了解我们的想法
all would be done in terms of uh you
一切都会根据你来完成
know me and others that aren't
认识我和其他不认识的人
committers contributing and so basically
提交者做出贡献，所以基本上
we would prototype something locally and
我们将在本地制作原型，
then just without Jenkins maybe on our
然后就没有詹金斯
own machines and then submit a change
自己的机器，然后提交更改
and that that you know the the committee
而且你知道委员会
will try it out on Jenkins then is that
将在詹金斯上尝试一下，然后是
what you're saying yes this is exactly
你说的是，这正是
what I said okay okay thank you
我说的好吧好吧谢谢
we still have two minutes are there any
我们还有两分钟吗
more questions
更多问题
okay no questions so it looks like we
好的，没有问题，所以看起来像我们
finished so thanks everyone for
完成了，所以谢谢大家
participation and again if you have any
参与，如果有的话，再次参加
questions if you would like to
问您是否要
self-assign I provided all information
自我分配我提供了所有信息
and we have that Eva J built made in
我们有Eva J内置的
place there you can ask questions thank
在那里你可以问问题谢谢
you very much for finish
非常感谢你
you're doing what
你在做什么